Guide to the Duke Gardens Foundation records, 1912-2002 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
- Legal Records, 1958-1999 (Box 106)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Albert E. Sendgikoski, 1970 Oct 23 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Francis A. Comstock, 1970 Oct 29 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Albert E. Sendgikoski, 1970 Nov 16 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition of Wesley J. Rose, 1970 Dec 1 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition of William H. Klein, PhD, 1970 Dec 2 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and memoranda regarding DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc., 1970 Dec 15 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - architectural drawings from URI, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Comstock diary entries, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Comstock letters to Eaton regarding Lord & Burnham contract, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. -correspondence and memoranda related to lawsuit, 1970 (1 of 2) (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. -correspondence and memoranda related to lawsuit, 1970 (2 of 2) (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Cox Files, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Defendant's answers to Interrogation, 1970 (1 of 2) (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Defendant's answers to Interrogation, 1970 (1 of 2) (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Eaton letters to Comstock regarding Lord & Burnham, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Eaton letters to Universal, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Eaton to Stroock and Stroock, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Emerson to Eaton, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Hanger letters to Eaton (miscellaneous), 1970 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Hanger letters to Eaton regarding condition of garden (L & B exam), 1970 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Hanger letters to R.D.S. & B with technical data, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - letters to Lord & Burnham regarding condition of gardens, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Lord & Burnham data prepared for R.D.S. & B, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - memo regarding conference with Jacobs & Hanger (includes black and white photographs), 1970 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - miscellaneous correspondence and architectural drawings, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - miscellaneous documents, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - miscellaneous notes and memos to proposed affidavit of Jacobs, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - notes on Lord & Burnham, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Papers Miss Duke obtained from Copeland, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Plaintiff's exhibits P-1 ID to P33 ID, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Plaintiff's exhibits P-34 ID to P75 ID, 1970 (1 of 2) (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Plaintiff's exhibits P-34 ID to P75 ID, 1970 (2 of 2) (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Plaintiff's exhibits P-76A ID to P102 ID, 1970 (1 of 2) (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Plaintiff's exhibits P-76A ID to P102 ID, 1970 (2 of 2) (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Duke Gardens Real Property Taxes, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Stroock and Stroock letters to Eaton, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. -studies and proposals of Universal, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Universal drawings, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Universal letters to Eaton, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Universal letters to Herzog, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Universal to Copeland, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Universal to Emerson, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. -Universal to Miss Duke, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. -correspondence and memoranda related to lawsuit, 1970-1971 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - exhibits marked during depositions, circal 1970-1971 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - memos regarding chronology, key partners to litigation and terminology, circa 1970-1971 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - outlines of testimony of expert witnesses and deposition testimony, 1970-1971 (1 of 2) (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - outlines of testimony of expert witnesses and deposition testimony, 1970-1971 (2 of 2) (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Trimmer: Sterling vs. Duke Gardens Foundations, 1970-1971 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    Access restricted
  - General correspondence from the office of Basil Hanger, 1970-1972 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Duke Gardens Federal Income Tax and Exemptions for Tax Year 1970, 1970-1973 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Doris Duke, 1971 Jan 20 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Doris Duke, 1971 Feb 3 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition of Charles E. Rahilly, 1971 Apr 19 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition of Saul T. Jacobs, 1971 Apr 19 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Accepted contract - Lord & Burnham restoration, 1971 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence regarding glass requirements, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Cost of Edwardian garden, House No. 26. Also Tropical garden, House No. 22, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Cost of Indo-Persian garden, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Cost of Italian garden, House No. 24, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Cost of semi-tropical garden, House No. 23, Colonial garden, House No. 25, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - subjects to be covered by testimony of Lord & Burnham, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Signed contract with Lord & Burnham regarding renovation to Duke Gardens, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence regarding possible litigation against Duke Gardens (Travers), 1972 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation vs. Blodwyn Traver and Harold Traver, 1972-1976 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Traver vs. Duke Gardens Foundation, 1973-1977 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Various contracts for restoration to gardens, 1973-1978 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Proposed contract between Duke Gardens Foundation and Lord & Burnham and DGF and Roper IBG for renovations to gardens, 1975, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Insurance letters from New York Office (Duke Business Office), 1975-1981 (1 of 4) (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Insurance letters from New York Office (Duke Business Office), 1975-1981 (2 of 4) (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Insurance letters from New York Office (Duke Business Office), 1975-1981 (3 of 4) (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Insurance letters from New York Office (Duke Business Office), 1975-1981 (4 of 4) (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Contract between Duke Gardens Foundation and Allied Boiler Repair Co., 1976 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Boiler and machinary insurance policy with Alexander & Alexander, 1977-1978 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Rebuilding the English Garden, 1979-1980 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Orchid Range - transfer of buildings, 1980-1984 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Baine vs. Duke Gardens Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation Workplace Survey Identification Data, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Gas Easement, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Insurance for Duke Gardens Foundation covered by KSH Group, Inc., 1993 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Underground storage tank registration certificate, 1993 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Contract approvals, 1998 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Contract approvals, 1999 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Emerson to Miss Duke, undated (Box 119, Folder 10)
- Architectural Records, 1912-1982 and undated (Box 119)
  The records document the proposed design, alterations and renovations of a variety of gardens and structures at Duke Gardens from numerous architects and engineering firms. Many of the records are from Lord & Burnham, the firm that designed and constructed the original greenhouse at Duke Farms and continued working with the Duke Gardens Foundation until the 1970s. Includes diazo prints, ink on tracing paper, and photostat copies.
  Digital use copies exist for some of the architectural records and have been identified below. Digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access please contact a reference archivist prior to visiting the library.
  - [Pedestal Sketch of McKinley Monument]. [Trentanove, Gaetano]. [c.1909]. Ink. (Opaperfolder C1D8F9, Box 119)
  - Staking Plan for French Garden. Innocenti & Webel. 1959 Jun 15. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities Duke Gardens Foundation (shows foundation and a pond). Raritan Valley Engineering/Traced by Mike Siroki. 1965 Feb 25. Pencil on vellum. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (shows fountain, Houses 27, 28, 30, 24, Admin. Office, Main Bldg. & Greenhouse) Duke Gardens Foundation. Raritan Valley Engineering/Traced by Mike Siroki. 1965 Feb 25. Pencil on vellum. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (shows Highway 206 and telephone cable) Duke Gardens Foundation. Raritan Valley Engineering/Traced by Mike Siroki. 1965 Feb 25. Pencil on vellum. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (shows shed, Admin. Office & garage) Duke Gardens Foundation. Raritan Valley Engineering/Traced by Mike Siroki. 1965 Feb 25. Pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (shows Coach Barn) Duke Gardens Foundation. Raritan Valley Engineering/Traced by Mike Siroki. 1965 Feb 25. Pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (shows telephone lines and manholes from Route 206 to display gardens complex) Duke Gardens Foundation. Mike Siroki/[Capitol Electric/Ralph Epright]. 1965 Feb 25; 1981-1982. Pencil on diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (shows Duke Gardens and residence underground power lines). Raritan Valley Engineering/Traced by Mike Siroki. 1965 Feb 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (shows foundation and a pond), Duke Gardens Foundation 8 of 11. Raritan Valley Engineering/Traced by Mike Siroki. 1965 Feb 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (shows Central RR of NJ), 4 of 7. Drawn by T.S.H. 1964 Nov 12. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (shows Central RR of NJ and pond). Traced by Mike Siroki. 1965 Feb 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (shows Coach Barn), 5 of 7. Drawn by T.S.H. 1964 Nov 12. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities Duke Gardens Foundation (shows telephone connections with Orchid Range complex). 1964 Nov 16; 1965 Feb 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities Duke Gardens Foundation (shows foundation and pond), 7 of 7. Drawn by T.S.H. 1964 Nov 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (shows pond), 6 of 8. Drawn by T.S.H. 1964 Nov 20. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities Duke Gardens Foundation (shows locations of pipes, pumps, septic tanks and distribution boxes related to the gardens), 2 of 11. Raritan Valley Engineering/ S.C.M, K.N. 1964 Jul 29; revised 1965 Jan 26. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Greenhouse Layout, 9 of 11. Raritan Valley Engineering/ R.S. 1965 Jan 22. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Greenhouse Layout, 10 of 11. Raritan Valley Engineering/ R.S. 1965 Jan 22. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Greenhouse Layout, 11 of 11. Raritan Valley Engineering/ R.S. 1965 Jan 22. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (3 of 3). Raritan Valley Engineering/ K.N. 1964 Oct 15. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - Plan of Above & Below Ground Utilities (2 of 3). Raritan Valley Engineering/ K.N. 1964 Oct 9. Diazo with pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D1F1, Box 119)
  - [Lattice Garden]. Savary & Glaeser, Inc./ J.H.G. 1968 Oct 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F2, Box 119)
  - Balustrades Design (2 of 5). Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Apr 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F2, Box 119)
  - Grille Scheme #1. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Jun 21. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F2, Box 119)
  - Grille Scheme #2. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Jun 21. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F2, Box 119)
  - Grille Scheme #3. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Jun 21. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F2, Box 119)
  - Grille Scheme #4. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Jun 21. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F2, Box 119)
  - Grille Scheme #5. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Jun 21. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F2, Box 119)
  - Grille Scheme #6. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Jun 21. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F2, Box 119)
  - Grille Scheme #7. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Jun 21. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F2, Box 119)
  - Chinese Garden. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Aug 12. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F3, Box 119)
  - Chinese Garden, Scheme I. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Mar 10. Diazo; Diazo with watercolor. (Opaperfolder C2D1F3, Box 119)
  - A Study of a Chinese Garden. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Apr 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F3, Box 119)
  - Grading Plan - Chinese Garden. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Apr 18. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F3, Box 119)
  - Special Outdoor Roadway Flood Light. Kliegl Brothers. 1965 Jan 15. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F4, Box 119)
  - Proposed Greenhouse Renovation of Duke Gardens Foundation [Plan, Side Elevations, Sections]. Lord & Burnham/G.W.R. 1970 Aug 26. Diazo, diazo with pen. (Opaperfolder C2D1F4, Box 119)
  - Landscape Plan, Greenhouse Courtyard. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Nov 19. Pencil on vellum. (Opaperfolder C2D1F4, Box 119)
  - A Tropical Garden. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Sep 18. Diazo; Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D1F6, Box 119)
  - Sunken Garden Survey, Maintenance Building Survey, Sheet 3. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1961 Jul 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F6, Box 119)
  - Revised Plan of Connection of Grapery & Melon House at North East Corner of Range. [Lord & Burnham]. 1912 Apr 30. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F6, Box 119)
  - South Elevation - Desert, Chinese & Japanese Gardens. Horowitz & Wirth/ B.P. 1974 Apr 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F6, Box 119)
  - Proposed Changes to Present Range of Glass. Lord & Burnham. 1912 Mar 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D1F6, Box 119)
  - Japanese Rock Garden - Spring Flower Plan. Undated. Watercolor on drafting cloth. (Opaperfolder C2D1F7, Box 119)
  - Florida Patio - Proposed Landscape Design. Boynton Landscape Co. 1959 Sep 4. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F8, Box 119)
  - Proposed Storage Building. Designed Structures, Inc. 1970 Feb 4. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F8, Box 119)
  - [Indo - Persian Garden]. URI Dekosit/ B.W. 1970 Apr 1. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F8, Box 119)
  - Half-Template of Panel "A" Screen. URI Dekosit/ A.E.S. 1970 May 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F8, Box 119)
  - Details of Screen. URI Dekosit/ A.E.S. 1970 May 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F8, Box 119)
  - Half Size Layout of Top Curve. URI Dekosit/ A.E.S. 1970 May 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F8, Box 119)
  - [Elevations of Panels I & N]. URI Dekosit/ A.E.S. 1970 May 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F8, Box 119)
  - Half Size Layout of Top Curve. URI Dekosit/ A.E.S. 1970 May 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F8, Box 119)
  - Ground - Plan View of the Conservatories and Greenhouses. Allan F. Gill. 1970 Oct. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F9, Box 119)
  - Proposed Rehabilitation and Restoration of Italian Gardens House #24. Lord & Burnham/ F.H. 1972 Mar 14. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F9, Box 119)
  - [Indo-Persian Garden Panels]. URI Dekosit/ B.W. 1970 Apr 1. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F9, Box 119)
  - Orchid Range. Undated. Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D1F9, Box 119)
  - Existing Layout Orchid Range Greenhouses. Undated. Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D1F9, Box 119)
  - [Greenhouse Gardens - Forecourt/Sunken Garden Plan]. Innocenti & Webel. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F10, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens [Forecourt/Sunken Garden Plan]. Innocenti & Webel. Undated. Diazo and pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D1F10, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens [Forecourt/Sunken Garden Plan]. Innocenti & Webel. Undated. Diazo and colored pencil; Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D1F10, Box 119)
  - Elevations of Palm and Aquatic Houses. [Lord & Burnham]. 1900 May. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F10, Box 119)
  - Palm House & Aquatic House. Horowitz & Wirth. 1975 Sep 11. Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D1F10, Box 119)
  - Trellis for Beds in Greenhouse of Mr. J.B. Duke. Lord & Burnham. 1900 Sep. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D1F10, Box 119)
    Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
  - [Orchid Range]. [Lord & Burnham]/D.B.M. [Circa 1900-1903]. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D1F10, Box 119)
  - Cast Stone Posts & Rail. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 May 26. Pencil on tracing paper. (Opaperfolder C2D1F11, Box 119)
  - Front View of Pavilion for Chinese Garden. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Feb 14. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F11, Box 119)
  - Bridge Design of Chinese Garden. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Feb 14. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F11, Box 119)
  - Moongate. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Apr 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F11, Box 119)
  - A Chinese Garden for Duke Farms (3 different renderings). Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Aug 12. Diazo; Silver Halide. (Opaperfolder C2D1F11, Box 119)
  - Perspective View of Chinese Garden. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Apr 6. Diazo and colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D1F11, Box 119)
  - A Chinese Garden Design. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Jan 14. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F11, Box 119)
  - Revised Plan of Chinese Garden. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Apr 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F12, Box 119)
  - Chinese Garden Plan. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 May 31. Pencil; Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F12, Box 119)
  - Chinese Garden Plan. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Jun 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F12, Box 119)
  - Pavilion Grille Detail. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Apr 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F12, Box 119)
  - Pavilion Detail. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Apr 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F12, Box 119)
  - Chinese Garden, Scheme II. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Mar 12. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F12, Box 119)
  - Plan for Moongate & Wall. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Jun 27. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D1F12, Box 119)
  - Heating Plan. Lord & Burnham / M.A. 1959 Jan 30. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F1, Box 119)
  - Site Plan of Proposed Individual Septic Systems for Four Dwellings. Raritan Valley Engineering/ S.C.M. 1964 Jul 29. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - Proposed Greenhouse Renovation. Lord & Burnham/ F.H. 1971 Mar 23; revised 1971 Apr 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - Pedestal for Statue - Elevations and Section Poured in Place. Donald Pantel/C.A.T. 1964 Jul 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - Pedestal for Statue - Plot Plan - Elevations. Donald Pantel/C.A.T. 1964 Jul 27. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - Pedestal for Statue. Donald Pantel/C.A.T. 1964 Jul 29. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - Map on Water Mains and Sewers in Conj with New Green Houses & Sunken Garden on the Est of J.B. Duke Somerville, NJ. I.J. Shaffer. 1913 Sep 1. Photocopy; Positive photostat. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - [Orchid Range]. [Lord & Burnham]. 1900 May. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - Greenhouse Extension. 1961. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - Proposed System of Pipe Lines for New Greenhouses & Ajct. Surroundings. I.J. Shaffer. 1912. Blueprint on linen. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - [Heating Pipes]. 1963. Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - North Gable Elevation, Edwardian Garden (House No. 26). Lord & Burnham/F.H. 1972 Oct 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - Storage Room for Duke's Gardens. Cunningham & Delvecchio. 1961 Oct 30. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - Storage Room for Duke's Gardens (Revised drawing). Cunningham & Delvecchio. 1961 Nov 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F2, Box 119)
  - Semi-Tropical Garden House No. 23 and Colonial-American Garden House No. 25. Lord & Burnham / F.H. 1973 Jul 23. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - Map of Survey, Duke Gardens Foundation. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1970 Feb 23. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - Geometry for Greenhouse Arch. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1971 Apr 7. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - Covered Walk, Dwg 1. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Nov. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - Covered Walk, Dwg 2. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Nov. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - Covered Walk, Dwg 3. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Nov. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - Typical Frame Details, Covered Walk & Bridge. Dwg 4. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Nov. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - Typical Details, Rail Detail, Dwg 5. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Nov. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - Typical Details, Corner Roof Framing. Dwg 6. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Nov. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - Covered Bridge. Dwg 7. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Nov. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - [Air Conditioning English & Japanese Gardens]. Brewer. [1963]. Negative Photostat. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - Balcony in Lattice House. John [R.] Hecht, 1963 Jan 9. Pen. (Opaperfolder C2D2F4, Box 119)
  - Plot Plan. Lord & Burnham. 1959 May 7. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F5, Box 119)
  - [Schematic Wiring Diagram, Powervent]. Lord & Burnham. [1926]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F5, Box 119)
  - Block Plan of Steam System. Lord & Burnham/ J.K., L.R.W. 1926 Jan 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F5, Box 119)
  - Details of Persian Garden at Connection to Japanese & Tropical Gardens. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1971 Apr 27. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F5, Box 119)
  - Italian Gardens - Reconstruction, Rear Elevation, Front Elevation. URI Dekosit/ K.C.E. 1970 Apr 13. Sepia diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F5, Box 119)
  - New Bulb Cellar. URI Dekosit/ M.D.S. 1970 Apr 2. Sepia Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F5, Box 119)
  - [Indo-Persian Garden]. URI Dekosit/ B.W. 1970 Apr 1. Sepia diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D2F5, Box 119)
  - Greenhouse for Mr. J.B. Duke. Horace Trumbauer, architect. 1909 Apr. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D2F5, Box 119)